<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="h18e38c09g1b5bg44f4g8c45g0e9d5f224084" version="1">Shaman</content>
	<content contentuid="h8fd328bagd60eg4ec5ga69dg9d08e253e7db" version="1">Before the gods took notice of mortals and bestowed power upon Clerics and Paladins, Shamans served as protectors and guides. Using ancient techniques, Shamans were able to bind spirits to Totems, small objects of spiritual significance, and channel that power for good of their people. </content>
	<content contentuid="h5510b3efgf77dg4201g9d61ga2d53610c7b7" version="1">Shamans bind and deal with the primal spirits of nature to fuel their magics and pursue their own ends.</content>
	<content contentuid="hba5aa2a9gb3c0g4d87g97f2gcc45a0a47028" version="1">Sacred Focus</content>
	<content contentuid="h64019770g015bg4ac5gab03ge1b2da00f184" version="1">In order to channel the supernatural power of spirits without being consumed, Shamans must draw this wondrous power through the strongest aspect of themselves. You must choose to channel your power through your Body, Heart, Mind, or Soul.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a47883dg5018g4e74gacb1gaf30b1a2a954" version="1">Sacred Focus: Body</content>
	<content contentuid="h6e794e02g5f26g4e3eg8e24g56102dbfee06" version="1">You channel spiritual power through your body, bending the spirits to your will with physical might. When you choose this Sacred Focus your hit point maximum increases by 1, and it increases by 1 again each time you gain a level in this class.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1eca09agfe87g47a1ga70bg0c363d7fe8aa" version="1">Sacred Focus: Heart</content>
	<content contentuid="hf3eeee19g29d8g41dega97ege29cf6e3edcf" version="1">You channel spiritual power into your heart and overwhelm spirits with powerful emotions. You have advantage against being Frightened or Charmed.</content>
	<content contentuid="h78e5b33ege4eag435ega895g90db163b2442" version="1">Sacred Focus: Mind</content>
	<content contentuid="h77be164dgaea5g4334gae14ge395b618d340" version="1">You channel spiritual power through your mind, manipulating the spirits with your wit. Whenever you would make an ability check or a saving throw that uses your Intelligence score, you can choose to use your Wisdom score instead.</content>
	<content contentuid="h16f590baga061g4a01g8611gaf787cd51ecc" version="1">Sacred Focus: Soul</content>
	<content contentuid="h881a2358g49ffg44d0gb9d8g2dfe28e43fad" version="1">You channel spiritual power through your soul, your serenity soothes spirits and wards you from harm. While not wearing armor or wielding a shield, your Armor Class is equal to 10 + your Dexterity modifier + your Wisdom modifier.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5d2acb17g0bb2g43d8g84f2g99f9329700e9" version="1">Totemic Assault</content>
	<content contentuid="hea56aaf4gc5e5g4b80gafd3gc1a8ad65dce9" version="1">You can temporarily unleash the primal spirits bound within your Totems to assault your foes. You can use your action to force one creature you can see to make a Charisma saving throw. On a failed save, it takes [1]. This damage scales with your cantrips.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6bb17decg7fb1g49c4gbea9gc17cd76998fa" version="1">Primal Magic Spell Slots</content>
	<content contentuid="h49f493cag90afg417bgb7eeg319b7756ca0e" version="1">Used to cast Shaman spells. Regain Primal Magic Spell Slots by taking a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h09e4a89cgfe29g4a31gba02g90ea208b07d4" version="1">Otherworldly Grasp</content>
	<content contentuid="he7b4b1f7gc99ag4945g9a3bg4ea70d99cbbc" version="1">You channel necrotic spiritual power to your hand, changing it into a withered specter of itself. Make a melee spell attack against a creature within your reach. On hit, the creature takes [1] necrotic damage, and you gain [2] temporary hit points which lasts until the start of your next turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h620c3109g751fg419fg8f26ga078df0f26d1" version="1">Ghastly Flight</content>
	<content contentuid="h2b608d1fg04d4g4b00ga928g2d74f2359143" version="1">You release a malevolent spirit that flies out from you in a direction of your choice. Each creature within the line must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, creatures take [1] and cannot regain hit points until the start of your next turn. On a success, creatures take half as much damage and can regain hit points as normal.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8be68ccdg2d67g466dgb1d1gfb38cbc58f47" version="1">Primal Magic Spell Slots</content>
	<content contentuid="h0c455adcg1019g40b0g80f1g2eb8b9d087ad" version="1">You now have [1] Level [2] Primal Magic Spell Slots which refresh on a Short or Long Rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4c964b55g604cg4086g95c7ge883e60c1ceb" version="1">Used to cast Shaman spells.</content>
	<content contentuid="h14e4b791g37c8g47c5g95dfg6cee01e8454b" version="1">Totemic Cowl</content>
	<content contentuid="h0c15a94ag4957g4314g8e64g37f619425682" version="1">You touch a willing creature. Until the spell ends, it is cloaked in a ghostly cowl, and any damage it takes is reduced by [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h3d6d62aeg9078g4115gae2fg5b7a50debb29" version="1">For each spell slot level used above the 2nd reduce damage by an additional 1.</content>
	<content contentuid="h34be756eg6951g4a76g9f62ga53cbaabdf61" version="1">Dire Wail</content>
	<content contentuid="h510c9553g0388g45c2g8021g12a53db6b8af" version="1">You let forth a wail filled with otherworldly power. Enemies must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take [1] and start Bleeding for 2 turns.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6e84ad2cgc013g4df8g85c2g893b1ebc9c0f" version="1">Spiritual Sundering</content>
	<content contentuid="hafd2f0ebg7c19g453dgb10fg334c61b70adc" version="1">Cast out a ball of spiritual energy. Enemies in the area must make a Charisma save or take [1] and become afflicted by Spiritual Torment, receiving  -1d6 to all Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma saves they make for 10 turns or until they save. </content>
	<content contentuid="he62aa0e7g7899g4fefg8265g14e3ca94bdba" version="1">Dawn</content>
	<content contentuid="hbb65e32dg966dg401agb307g790af2f8f0db" version="1">The light of dawn shines down on a location and damages any creature that enters the beam or starts its turn in the light. This counts as Sunlight and you can use a bonus action to move the beam [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h6dd716e6g29f0g4a01ga307gc057a67dc083" version="1">Investiture of Flame</content>
	<content contentuid="h8031c826g00afg4f5cga6cfgc571b50a17b2" version="1">Flames race across your body, shedding bright light. For the spell’s duration you gain the following effects: You are Immune to Fire and Resistant to Cold Damage, enemies who enter or start their turn within [1] of you take [2], and you may use an action to cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_Zone_Investiture_Flame"&gt;Roiling Inferno&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
	<content contentuid="h700f95fbg2929g4b5cga06bg587d76fa7fda" version="1">Roiling Inferno</content>
	<content contentuid="hfa294bb9gee41g49fegbb89g8bb5a4572bbd" version="1">Lash out with a line of Flames dealing 4d8 fire damage to all creatures.</content>
	<content contentuid="h325c7679g0ca7g48e7gaf35g31c389601ed1" version="1">Investiture of Ice</content>
	<content contentuid="haeb2c7a0gbaddg4a31g877dgf4a0180eff7f" version="1">Frost and ice spreads across your body. For the spell’s duration you gain the following effects: You are Immune to Cold and Resistant to Fire Damage,you cannot slip on ice, and at the end of each turn the area around you turns into ice, and you may use an action to cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_Zone_Investiture_Ice"&gt;Tundra's Lash&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
	<content contentuid="hcfa4e99bgd956g40f1gace2g4f82cd11e2d1" version="1">Tundra's Lash</content>
	<content contentuid="h2e00a114gc7cfg42feg8f01g830bd21027a2" version="1">Lash out with a cone of ice dealing 4d6 cold damage to all creatures and potentially halving their movespeed.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1e777f3bg4d6dg4208ga458g999145369439" version="1">Investiture of Wind</content>
	<content contentuid="h40f0dc12g48bbg4a77gbba6g482bc8b6f4de" version="1">Until the spell ends, wind whirls around you, and you gain the following benefits: Ranged Weapon Attacks have Disadvantage against you, you can fly, and you may use an action to cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_Target_Investiture_Wind"&gt;Buffeting Winds&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
	<content contentuid="hf3a30419g3684g47b7gb016g3def3cea5883" version="1">Buffeting Winds</content>
	<content contentuid="h9cafabf2g28bag4a18g9cbcg8c47f81491d2" version="1">Create a burst of incredible wind in an area you can see. Creatures in the area must make a Constitution save or take 2d10 damage and be pushed back.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf286f0d4g6afdg40c1gbddbg3a0e51edac6d" version="1">Spirit Warrior</content>
	<content contentuid="h27c21a27g1024g4d12g8227g5493cab6b8a1" version="1">Serving as the guardians of sacred groves and places of great spiritual power, Spirit Warriors draw on the power of ancient spirits to enhance their physical form. When they allow these incorporeal beings to walk the world through their physical bodies, they gain increased physical and martial abilities.</content>
	<content contentuid="h53e677abgeb47g45b1ga66ag16c953505049" version="1">Ancestral Knowledge</content>
	<content contentuid="h22a97e39gf3b4g4b13g8e85g873bb12354b2" version="1">Spirits of ancient warriors grant you their lifetimes' worth of combat experience. You gain proficiency with medium armor and all martial weapons.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0aa4fdc4gf5c5g4fc1gb16dge188c61d925e" version="1">Totemic Weapon</content>
	<content contentuid="h05d6d33ag23cfg482cg8b10g3901d7ac87c7" version="1"> You can bind powerful spirits to your weapons for use in battle. At the end of a short rest, you can perform a ritual to bind one of your spirits to a melee weapon you're wielding. The weapon becomes magical and you use your Wisdom for it's Attack and Damage Rolls. The benefits last until the end of your next long rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7fc3bc14g532bg41d6gbc32gce72c9fa2832" version="1">Spirit of Challenge</content>
	<content contentuid="hf1798397gea42g4733gbe93gd621f55e98db" version="1"> This spirit compels your foes to stand and fight against you. The weapon becomes magical and you use your Wisdom for it's Attack and Damage Rolls. When you hit a creature with an attack with this weapon, it has disadvantage on any attacks it makes against creatures other than you until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc8e4f0b9g9b1eg4c6cgaed4g9601c114dd6f" version="1"> This creature is compelled by one of your spirits to fight you. It has disadvantage when attacking other targets.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd64cbe1eged79g483bg9f9dgb13b3d90be9c" version="1">Spirit of Draining</content>
	<content contentuid="h9b035a6cg833fg40cdg9cdbg425a0391b3cd" version="1"> This spirit siphons the life force of other creatures to restore you. The weapon becomes magical and you use your Wisdom for it's Attack and Damage Rolls. You also gain a special attack that can be used once per turn which deals Necrotic Damage and gives you Temporary HP equal to your Wisdom Modifier. The cooldown of this attack is refreshed if it misses.</content>
	<content contentuid="h40f548c2ge916g4cacgbdcag02693042418f" version="1">Draining Strike</content>
	<content contentuid="h95ca28bag71efg4934g912ag2ba0935bc772" version="1"> Let one of your Spirits flow through your swing. This attack deals Necrotic Damage and gives you Temporary HP equal to your Wisdom Modifier. The cooldown of this attack is refreshed if it misses.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcee741b1gae69g4634g9c75g6bfc4e59b3ae" version="1">Spirit of Might</content>
	<content contentuid="he7165934g03e7g4e7fg93f8g29720c41dea2" version="1"> This spirit draws out the full potential of your body. While wielding this weapon you gain a bonus to Strength checks and saving throws equal to your Wisdom modifier. The weapon becomes magical and you use your Wisdom for it's Attack and Damage Rolls. Moreover, you have advantage on attack rolls with this weapon against any creature that is grappled by you. </content>
	<content contentuid="h76632ac5g8688g498egb870g096fbc1c2dd5" version="1">You can attack twice, instead of once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn. Moreover, you can cast a Shaman cantrip you know, or use Totemic Assault in place of one of your attacks.</content>
	<content contentuid="h66c2a5d8g44dbg46e0g8c32gab30270fbb24" version="1">Warrior of the Grave</content>
	<content contentuid="h845c90d5g741fg4ee4gb5abg7b5944e4023a" version="1">You can offer your very life force to the spirit realm to resist the grasp of death. Once per Short Rest, when you are reduced to 0 hit points but not killed outright you regain 1 Hit Point. </content>
	<content contentuid="h3722f63bg8e1fg44dbg9f74g17bdf0dee545" version="1">Spiritual Champion</content>
	<content contentuid="hd5e42593gbbeeg4927gb385g2dacb1267681" version="1"> You can offer the spirits full control of your body, granting you temporary mystical power. As a bonus action, you can enter a possessed state, gaining the following benefits for 1 minute: You gain the effects of Blade Ward, you may Dash as a Bonus Action, and once per turn when you hit an enemy with a melee weapon attack you may inflict an additional [1]. You can do this Once per Short Rest for free and can be used again by expending a Primal Magic Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h145fe01eg7c23g4228ga9c2gbfd05f6540c8" version="1">Spiritual Detonation</content>
	<content contentuid="h134608e4gab39g4e33ga3c5g13977c9bd3ae" version="1"> Once per turn when you hit an enemy with a melee attack you may deal an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h2b2e664dg3d5ag4384gb167gd20a5cd7974a" version="1">Spiritual Acceleration</content>
	<content contentuid="h46f46f3aga920g4b39g8c4fg252674fa5e66" version="1">Curse Binder</content>
	<content contentuid="h57b136f0gae1dg45afg8ebcg7ea9da226435" version="1">While most Shamans use the power of spirits to work magics and heal the sick, some twist this connection, binding sinister spirits to their foes. Known as Curse Binders, these Shamans wield the sinister spiritual power present in the world. Often apprentices of hags or entities from the Shadowfell, they use ancient techniques to afflict their foes with hexes and curses.</content>
	<content contentuid="he698d680g8131g4f95ga1aag0165ebaf94ae" version="1">Evil Eye</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f6a7114ge10fg47e5g903ag12836c93ab62" version="1">You can curse with a glance. As a reaction, when an enemy succeeds on an attack roll, or saving throw, you can impose disadvantage on its roll. You can use this reaction a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier, and you regain all expended uses when you finish a long rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="h10fc7a17gc636g45a4g9cc8g8afaa9c7285e" version="1">Evil Eye Charges</content>
	<content contentuid="haceabbfdg58c0g40d1ga0bcgbd22e5554e20" version="1">You can use your Evil Eye a number of times per long rest equal to your Wisdom Modifier</content>
	<content contentuid="hee485c58g4681g4b1ag9a8eg2ca1beca65fa" version="1">Totemic Curse: Bane</content>
	<content contentuid="h0cd40c00gc8cbg4385gb16ega7bbc9db92bf" version="1"> You bind spirits of pain, suffering, and despair to your will, using them to inflict curses upon your enemies. When a creature fails its saving throw against Totemic Assault afflict it with: Whenever it makes an ability check or an attack roll, it must subtract your Wisdom modifier from the result of its roll.</content>
	<content contentuid="h20a0675fg7506g4687ga1c4g27422fbd5215" version="1"> This creature receives a [1] penalty to Attack Rolls and Skill Checks</content>
	<content contentuid="h5856ae9bg21afg418bg99ccg017381cffe30" version="1">Totemic Curse: Hex</content>
	<content contentuid="hd176deeag0490g4326g8f26gd555624c3f18" version="1"> You bind spirits of pain, suffering, and despair to your will, using them to inflict curses upon your enemies. When a creature fails its saving throw against Totemic Assault afflict it with: It cannot regain hit points, and when it takes damage it takes an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h544da829g86f0g456aga538g6fe4b84f181e" version="1"> This creature cannot heal and whenever it is damage by a Spell or Attack it takes [1]</content>
	<content contentuid="hfd0e1099g3f98g45dfgb65ag8c42aa8c0e1e" version="1">Totemic Curse: Slow</content>
	<content contentuid="h594c2c8ag73e2g4ab6ga8b5g176f188147a0" version="1"> You bind spirits of pain, suffering, and despair to your will, using them to inflict curses upon your enemies. When a creature fails its saving throw against Totemic Assault afflict it with: Its speed is reduced by a total number of feet equal to 5 times your Wisdom modifier.</content>
	<content contentuid="he3231ce1g5219g4de6g9097gc77a98f1a98c" version="1"> This creatures Movement Speed is reduced by [1]</content>
	<content contentuid="h4c363829gf6fag4f70g980cg422a24d2e659" version="1">Shamanistic Ward</content>
	<content contentuid="h23a69a98gd7b4g4ff3gb549g9aeb709444bb" version="1">Sinister spirits ward you against elemental assaults. Once per long rest, choose either acid, cold, fire, lightning, necrotic, poison, psychic, radiant, or thunder. Until the end of your next long rest, you are resistant to that damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h611f083cga5e2g4649g9988g739a16c29710" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Acid</content>
	<content contentuid="h1fd09182g16fcg4a61gb675gfcabe3d2ba22" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Cold</content>
	<content contentuid="h46c72db7gdbbcg4443ga0bfgb59300909780" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Fire</content>
	<content contentuid="h4e71d7bcgbb3cg404fgbffag5ac516d83a56" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Lightning</content>
	<content contentuid="h5b9a98afg4671g424fg8862gc48eeef1e0c0" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Necrotic</content>
	<content contentuid="hf87d3ef8g328ag41ceg8054g3d01fe65010e" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Poison</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb393eafgec54g4d5fga1eag914fc98fe4f6" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Psychic</content>
	<content contentuid="hcdc7071cg7081g4cd9gb4f3g9060e7be6bb4" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Radiant</content>
	<content contentuid="ha8945be5ge1cag4a54g910dgdfc648e5772f" version="1">Shamanistic Ward: Thunder</content>
	<content contentuid="hd0b019cag0d32g4450g8492g67a6643f99fe" version="1">Make yourself Resistant to [1] Damage until your next Long Rest</content>
	<content contentuid="ha66463d8g65a1g4d30g9e60g04e1fd63d44f" version="1">Your spirits shield you and make you Resistant to [1] Damage until your next Long Rest</content>
	<content contentuid="haa20ab4ag190fg4edagb936gb72b1d601820" version="1">Shamanistic Rebuke</content>
	<content contentuid="h39fc39f8g3a95g4e46g9300g3fbc2cfb795a" version="1">Your sinister spirits yearn to lash out. When you take Damage of a type that you resist, you can use Totemic Assault as a reaction, targeting your attacker.</content>
	<content contentuid="h07b492d7g768dg4dd4gb26ag9a9d28274406" version="1">Foul Conjuration</content>
	<content contentuid="h04d96422g0d6ag44c7gb157g40e9de64fb6a" version="1"> You have reached the apex of sinister shamanism, the ability to create corporeal bodies for the spirits you conjure. Once per Long Rest, you may cast Create Undead at 6th-level, without expending a spell slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3990df33g8b05g4242g9fa7g04d366229210" version="1">Witch Doctor</content>
	<content contentuid="h1542a79ag7fd3g4226gb21fg1a67db4773a4" version="1">Long before the gods took notice of mortals, Witch Doctors wandered the land, providing spiritual healing and medicine. Working in tandem with spirits of life, Witch Doctors heal the wounded and grant their allies mystical abilities. These sages are peaceful in nature and can often be found traveling the wilds tending to the spiritual needs of those they meet.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9f13eecagb724g4248gb57fgba7ba97fc80d" version="1">Life Bearer</content>
	<content contentuid="hdd55d41fg03c2g4617gb280gd31d6e60fa94" version="1"> You can channel spirits of abundance and life to heal others. As an action, you can touch a creature and cause it to regain hit points equal to 1d8 + your Wisdom modifier. This feature has no effect on undead creatures or constructs.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdab0c206gad30g454eg9291gb208e10a0840" version="1">Life Bearer Charges</content>
	<content contentuid="h51df80e5g6c22g4576g8605ged18a6c25b26" version="1">You can use your Life Bearer ability a number of times equal to your Shaman Level and regain all uses on a Long Rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="h402c4a5dg8fbdg40f7ga211gcd3930f4342a" version="1">Mystical Focus</content>
	<content contentuid="hff892a28g44c4g4f8dg92a9g5107d2068200" version="1">You work in tandem with the spirits bound to you, drawing out more of their power. When you use your action to cast one of your Witch Doctor Spells, or to use your Life Bearer ability, you can use Totemic Assault as a bonus action on that turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h45f837fbgec81g4de8ga1cdgb8693efba04c" version="1">Primal Magic Spell Slot Gained</content>
	<content contentuid="hcd0e3626g9a79g4c53g83d6g10a53d7728a5" version="1">You gain a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SB_ShamanSpellSlot"&gt;Primal Magic Spell Slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha2943191g3aa1g42ebg9924ga77d332f0dfb" version="1">Primal Magic Spell Slots</content>
	<content contentuid="hd7399243g91a1g4cb3g82d9g3013c130481c" version="1">You gain a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SB_ShamanSpellSlot"&gt;Primal Magic Spell Slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2ce438f8gc47fg4577g9a67g505838861879" version="1">Improved Shaman Spells</content>
	<content contentuid="h7da429bbgc7b0g4705g9655gaed04c90918a" version="1">Most of your Shaman spells have become stronger.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5aa14410g589eg4273gaa3fg4e86fb2d8520" version="1">Sacred Focus</content>
	<content contentuid="h2cdefc0fg6ecfg46fdga837gfc4b69421c16" version="1">In order to channel the supernatural power of spirits without being consumed, Shamans must draw this wondrous power through the strongest aspect of themselves.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0adb0744g8bf4g4ca7gad37gcb9db1539a00" version="1">Totemic Blessing</content>
	<content contentuid="h31ee17afg3cfbg48b9g94dag889ec1c0d9f1" version="1">You may bestow the powers of your Totems upon your allies. They gain the effects of the totem and you lose them until your next long rest. You may bestow a second Totem per long rest at 6th level and a 3rd Totem at 12th level.</content>
	<content contentuid="h719f5007g23e8g4a66g97d4g2b80b8b72fcd" version="1">You have been granted the Totem of the [1] until your next long rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="he4aa1dccga19ag4902ga27dg110c46743036" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Bear</content>
	<content contentuid="h90ebab9bg57b1g401agbfb1g83abe56e29e0" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Crossroads</content>
	<content contentuid="hfdac1a5fgd12ag464fga9bdg66ef396f7df1" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Eagle</content>
	<content contentuid="h648eaeecgc3ecg45b3g9884gabddcc09d108" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Earthquake</content>
	<content contentuid="h4e56e575g0156g48a1g93b4g97a135f1eb44" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Hound</content>
	<content contentuid="hd9dabff9g0723g4c11g8f49g2a3b875c7a3b" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Mountain</content>
	<content contentuid="h8b0cf020g0594g471dg90aeg4c7abd9025be" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Panther</content>
	<content contentuid="h15b5757dg1eeag406eg85ccga002b28c88f4" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Quagmire</content>
	<content contentuid="h8230c897ge5e5g4c8bgab45g6123892eaaa9" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Rains</content>
	<content contentuid="he476d9c4g2bbdg4e04ga94dgea969fd6deff" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Twilight</content>
	<content contentuid="h368a8281gd399g419eg8364g081d55a60d2c" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Whirlwind</content>
	<content contentuid="h70a3ae8egd758g40adgae03g9d69176369bf" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Winds</content>
	<content contentuid="hd2fb541cgf79dg48eega017g0d91978a0be8" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Eruption</content>
	<content contentuid="h44ae7a06gf329g4cfbg8a6bg9a110b0c2ff1" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Growth</content>
	<content contentuid="h90efcacag6a57g487agb4d1g364f971eb5b9" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Light</content>
	<content contentuid="h74e08e97g8d1eg4dd9ga315g5e40420f1603" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Mirth</content>
	<content contentuid="hccc80d3fgaebbg4301gb245gbfa1cc1f267b" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Mystic</content>
	<content contentuid="hed259ee3gbb9bg4dddg93c3ge5576c319f4a" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Wild</content>
	<content contentuid="h52a40290gd703g4c2cg97d6g5597da87513c" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Wrath</content>
	<content contentuid="h97484cbcg2432g4253g9480g258da8317a5f" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Hunt</content>
	<content contentuid="h2898ada8gcb19g441ag817dg2c63944322e6" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Sun</content>
	<content contentuid="h46e4b965g63c1g4859g948fg35a665ff0ab1" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Vine</content>
	<content contentuid="h13d629eagabf8g46c1ga55dg08709d8b5e01" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Eclipse</content>
	<content contentuid="hf54e1dcbgfa30g460dg9eccga3b9aeb39a68" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Sapling</content>
	<content contentuid="hbfda063fgb991g43dag8964gff79d2f8bcb3" version="1">Totemic Blessing: Skies</content>
	<content contentuid="hb5dbc2d8g68f5g43fbg99d2g6098116837ab" version="1">Bestow the Totem of [1] upon an ally.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd624bf2egc9b4g48dagbf7egd21f95060f17" version="1">Empowered Blessing</content>
	<content contentuid="h99e8f421gc8ffg4404g9f69gb23bd4244dc7" version="1"> Your allies can channel the spiritual power within your Totems. As an action on its turn, a creature that has one of your Totems bound to it can use Totemic Assault.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcc42b2cdgaaafg400egb511ga4d40e900106" version="1">Selfless Ward</content>
	<content contentuid="h21f43a0agf46fg448eg822ag068ba0271bbd" version="1">Your spirit is invigorated by the binding of Totems to your allies. You gain a +1 bonus to all saving throws for each of the Totems that you bind to another creature.</content>
	<content contentuid="hce3f7cebg2c96g4b11g89dage257a37c7113" version="1">Spiritual Awakening</content>
	<content contentuid="hee354cf2gb1c9g4a46g955agd333f76b7cb5" version="1">Your spiritual practice has filled you with an abundance of life-giving energy. Once per long rest when a an Ally is Downed you may restore [1] to that ally. You may use this additional times at the cost of a Primal Magic Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h85ccdae9g12cfg4b92ga70cg283cc73612fb" version="1">Greater Spirit of Death</content>
	<content contentuid="h29c6fefdg70bdg405dgb2a8g4657eb24c5d4" version="1">Spirits of Death are drawn from the Shadowfell, the Hells, or the Abyss. They lend Shamans their powerful sinister magic. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_FleshtoStone"&gt; Flesh to Stone&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h42ad8a60gdf96g4cf8g84e7gd488b6020922" version="1">Greater Spirit of Life</content>
	<content contentuid="hac72c2b8g58ccg4a0bg9645gfb0202321e53" version="1">Spirits of Life come to aid Shamans from the upper planes or the Feywild. They bless Shamans with mystic healing magic. Once per long rest you may cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_Heal"&gt;Heal&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h473a1515ga9b5g4d0egb47fg22d78de5dd1f" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Moon</content>
	<content contentuid="h97bbfcadgfca5g417egaec2g29b024fcb41a" version="1">Spirits of the Moon can be summoned from the Astral Sea or Ethereal Plane. They grant Shamans wondrous magic power. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_GlobeOfInvulnerability"&gt; Globe of Invulnerability&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2a91156fg7f55g4012g8ba1gccbc7f7de3b0" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Sun</content>
	<content contentuid="h6112493ega12cg492fgb1edgbdacc3b3f284" version="1">Spirits of the Sun are drawn from places of powerful radiant magic. They lend Shamans restorative and purifying power. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_Sunbeam"&gt; Sunbeam&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb897d669g1dc4g4812g9467g1fa83d1cac06" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Inferno</content>
	<content contentuid="hcbf24ac0g3e56g4b99g85e1gccf53c2dc4d1" version="1">Spirits of the Inferno are summoned from the great Plane of Fire. They grant Shamans overwhelming destructive power. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_Investiture_Flame"&gt; Investiture of Flame&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h729ee980gf709g4871g9245g965d3037ded4" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Hurricane</content>
	<content contentuid="hab64b23agb937g424ag8d8ag33f9c96d6ade" version="1">Spirits of the Hurricane come to aid Shamans from the Elemental Plane of Air. They bless Shamans with the incredible power of the winds. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_Investiture_Wind"&gt; Investiture of Wind&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h835d13b7g2817g401cg859dg3905967a8a05" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Tundra</content>
	<content contentuid="h002c93aag9b0eg4276g83f2ga99e4fdc14bb" version="1">Spirits of the Tundra come to aid Shamans from the Elemental Plane of Ice. They bless Shamans with the chilling magic power. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_Investiture_Ice"&gt; Investiture of Ice&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h19b31a38gdbddg4f48gadb6g4066eecb78f4" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Sea</content>
	<content contentuid="h9d8eb868g079fg428eg9046gb5fd646b1c53" version="1">Spirits of the Sea are called up from the depths of the Plane of Water. They bestow Shamans with frigid ethereal magics. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_FreezingSphere"&gt; Otiluke's Freezing Sphere&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9002307bgf4aeg403bga5cdg1843de33674f" version="1">Greater Spirit of the Storm</content>
	<content contentuid="h8cd90367geb92g488fg9c0egc130d8f9b26e" version="1">Spirits of the Storm are drawn from the great tempests of the Plane of Air. They lend Shamans the wild magic of storms. Once per long rest you may cast&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_GreaterSpirit_ChainLightning"&gt; Chain Lightning&lt;/LSTag&gt; without using a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h15f8dc53gec6eg4e8agaae0g0d60ce02125f" version="1">Conduit of the Curse Bringers</content>
	<content contentuid="h2632b84dge664g48d6g86fag994d323cda9f" version="1">A relic that comes alive in the hands of a Curse Bringer. A potent conduit that channels the power of their bound spirits into those unfortunate enough to draw their ire.</content>
	<content contentuid="h498237fbge102g46f3g8fbag42e750ed1c84" version="1">Conduit of the Spirit Warriors</content>
	<content contentuid="heb679143g4cf8g4daaga9d9g787be27f0ea1" version="1">A relic that thrums with the memories of countless warriors. A potent conduit that channels the powers of a Spirit Warrior more fiercely than any other.</content>
	<content contentuid="h752eed14g79bbg4a9eg8d57g257016cb5c5c" version="1">Conduit of the Witch Doctors</content>
	<content contentuid="h3514f1b7g0ca2g48c9gbeb9g866985b29dbf" version="1">A relic that sings out with healing energies. A potent conduit that channels the power of your bound spirits into those in need of your healing.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc324fad1gf6e6g4cf1gb423g3274fa33c258" version="1">Spirit Bound</content>
	<content contentuid="h9a8462d6gc106g4137gaacdg42a68506f172" version="1">The magic bound to this staff reacts and changes as your command over your Primal Magic grows. Starting at Shaman level 4 you have +1 to your Spell Attack Rolls and Spell Save DC. Starting at level 6 your Totemic Assault can target 1 additional enemy. Starting at Level 8 you add your Wisdom Modifier to your Totemic Assault's Damage. Starting at level 10 you have +2 to your Spell Attack Rolls and Spell Save DC.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb84fcd8ag8c20g4d04gbbe3g4dddf0655b6b" version="1">The magic bound to this club reacts and changes as your command over your Primal Magic grows. This weapon becomes a +1 Weapon at Shaman level 3 and increases again at Levels 7 and 11. Starting at level 4 when this weapon is bound as your Totemic Weapon it deals an additional 1d4 damage. Starting at level 10 the extra damage increases to 1d6.</content>
	<content contentuid="hef9a4419g9fe6g4b79g9f80gf8d4bdf05435" version="1">The magic bound to this staff reacts and changes as your command over your Primal Magic grows. Starting at Shaman level 4 you have +1 to your Spell Attack Rolls and Spell Save DC. Starting at level 6 when you heal a creature with a leveled spell or your&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_Target_LifeBearer"&gt; Life Bearer&lt;/LSTag&gt; ability you add your Wisdom Modifier to the healing. Starting at Level 8&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="SB_Target_LifeBearer"&gt; Life Bearer's&lt;/LSTag&gt; range becomes [1]. Starting at level 10 you have +2 to your Spell Attack Rolls and Spell Save DC.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3af359d7g6dceg44a1g9c77g3fd97d420f3b" version="1">DW Testing</content>
	<content contentuid="ha074f65dge959g41a1g87f0gdbdeb00d3250" version="1">Totems</content>
	<content contentuid="hd102ce7eg2f50g49afgab5fg64f81005da2d" version="1">You learn to bind primal nature spirits into sacred Totems so that you may safely channel their mystical abilities.</content>
	<content contentuid="head093d0gfdf5g4021g8c5cgc1c1404bd826" version="1">Totem of the Bear</content>
	<content contentuid="hc09673d9g9fc0g47a7gbe9bgd10698d12fcd" version="1">You bind a minor bestial spirit that grants you the ferocity of a bear. As a bonus action, you can grow claws from your fingers. With your claws, your unarmed strikes deal magical slashing damage equal to 1d6 + your Strength modifier on hit. If you have two free hands, the d6 becomes a d8. You can use another bonus action to cause the claws to disappear.</content>
	<content contentuid="h89cb4477g880fg4bf3gbffbgf136be5c0d6e" version="1">Totem: Reveal Claws</content>
	<content contentuid="h7c9ec313gc50cg4037gb2dfgfd113654d985" version="1">You can bond with your Totem and grow claws from your fingers. With your claws, your unarmed strikes deal magical slashing damage equal to 1d6 + your Strength modifier on hit. If you have two free hands, the d6 becomes a d8.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf5628e37g6ed9g437eg8848gf9ba9e32c6a4" version="1">Totem: Retract Claws</content>
	<content contentuid="hefcde9e6g6f7dg4593g9cf8gfb95877f7c6e" version="1">You can retract your claws ending the effect.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3d71a0c3gfb3ag42ccg9ffbg1c59262fe3db" version="1">Totemic Swipe</content>
	<content contentuid="h02b59de9gbb8bg46b7g9739g643172a964b7" version="1">Strike out with your claws dealing [1] or dealing [2] instead if both of your hands are empty.</content>
	<content contentuid="h84bb8775gad9eg4d7agb883gda96ed5bc0da" version="1">Totem of the Crossroads</content>
	<content contentuid="h8d4f086ag2342g4a91g8c94g03851cd7b4c7" version="1">REQUIRES: Heart Sacred Focus
You bind a minor Fey spirit that allows you to converse with wild creatures in your own tongue. You are always under the effect of speak with animals while you are conscious.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f0317fcg1397g4ca3g95d7gde7fc943d9fc" version="1">Totem of the Eagle</content>
	<content contentuid="h57cc15dfg83bbg4db4g89ffg8ea84783d234" version="1">You bind a minor bestial spirit that grants you the sight of an eagle. You gain proficiency in Perception, and you have advantage on Perception checks</content>
	<content contentuid="h563d3275g7bd4g4614gacfdg5e66dac5b705" version="1">Totem of the Earthquake</content>
	<content contentuid="hf9f543ddged30g4706g8db7gec0a24a34421" version="1">You bind a spirit of earth that grants you destructive power. Once per turn when you hit with a melee weapon attack, you can deal an additional 1d6 damage of your weapon's type. This damage bonus increases as you gain Shaman levels; at 5th level (1d8), 10th level (1d10), and 15th level (1d12).</content>
	<content contentuid="h07773db9g93a5g4135gb7b5gbc82a7c54659" version="1">Unleash a Spirit of Earth on your enemy dealing an additional [1] damage of your weapons type.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd1cc0d25g271dg41b2g931bg26650e821e43" version="1">Totem of the Harvest</content>
	<content contentuid="h0d43f4cag0f5bg4e2fg8234g6772fc9d8a94" version="1">REQUIRES: Soul Sacred Focus
You bind a minor spirit of wild growth and bounty. You learn the spell Goodberry which you can cast once per Short Rest without expending a spell slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h557be28cg0a41g4593gba0cgf3308a986023" version="1">Totem of the Hound</content>
	<content contentuid="hb419bf25g6ebdg40a1g9bffg97273a02c0a9" version="1">You bind a minor bestial spirit that grants you the senses of a hound. You gain proficiency in Survival, and you have advantage on Survival checks</content>
	<content contentuid="hefb10318g5f0ag45a7g94d0gc7d0b0fb5a11" version="1">Totem of the Mountain</content>
	<content contentuid="habc18b5cgedf0g42b9gabceg9885f3dd02f3" version="1">REQUIRES: Body Sacred Focus
You bind a minor spirit of the earth that hardens your skin like that of solid rock. So long as you are not wearing any armor or wielding a shield, your Armor Class is equal to 13 + your Constitution modifier.</content>
	<content contentuid="h123b932fg2539g4091ga7a4g9487a5b01ee6" version="1">Totem of the Panther</content>
	<content contentuid="h4c7f888ag468bg4dd2g90a5g7490c9c000c0" version="1">You bind a minor bestial spirit that grants you the steps of a panther. You gain proficiency in Stealth, and you have advantage on Stealth checks</content>
	<content contentuid="hcd5a4345gd553g4297g84a3gfd50abe115f2" version="1">Totem of the Quagmire</content>
	<content contentuid="hf1aef0cfg2040g46d4g800cg122df5e6d518" version="1">REQUIRES: Mind Sacred Focus
 You bind a minor spirit of darkness that guards your mind and laces your words. You gain proficiency in Deception and Intimidation.</content>
	<content contentuid="h48624958ga0d0g47eegb63bg0f27382521c6" version="1">Totem of the Rains</content>
	<content contentuid="h0f0acfcag7335g46d4gadd8gda46f757bb1c" version="1">You bind a minor spirit of water that washes poison away like rain. You gain resistance to acid and poison damage, and you have advantage on saving throws to resist being poisoned.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb010643g9433g411cgabceg2e73de2216e1" version="1">Totem of Twilight</content>
	<content contentuid="haf1c947eg60d1g4259gbe2fg367905b38920" version="1">You bind a minor spirit of darkness that grants you enhanced sight in the shadows. You gain Darkvision to a range of [1]. At 5th level this becomes Devil's Sight, and you can see through magical darkness.</content>
	<content contentuid="h21286809g8debg45e9g81fcg4532adbddbf0" version="1">Totem of the Waves</content>
	<content contentuid="hdb40820cg3e23g4caaga0caga9ba4639f6a9" version="1">You bind a minor spirit of water that allows you to shift like the sea. Once per short Rest as a reaction when you take a critical hit, you can to turn it into a normal hit. When you reach 12th level in this class, you can use this reaction twice between each Short Rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="hddf178dag79eag48acg9224g1fcfacaaba18" version="1">Totem of the Whirlwind</content>
	<content contentuid="h8d51d231gf44dg48f3g862fg91825decc1b7" version="1">You bind a minor spirit of air that speeds your strikes. When you score a critical hit with a melee weapon attack, you can use your reaction to make another attack against that target.</content>
	<content contentuid="h82af5a82g46fbg4564g8b2bg9510ee6bbbff" version="1">Whirlwind Slash</content>
	<content contentuid="hc204f3cag02c2g4e9cg9228gf72f3af0d4ee" version="1">Totem of the Winds</content>
	<content contentuid="h140418fegc2b9g45c3g9624gdcbec3286726" version="1">You bind a minor spirit of the air which lends speed to your steps with a gust of mighty wind. Your walking speed increases by [1]. This bonus to your speed increases as you gain Shaman levels; at 5th level ([2]), 10th level, ([3]), and finally at 15th level ([4]).</content>
	<content contentuid="hacff76e1g2ff9g4b8bgbeb9gac83543efc03" version="1">Totem of the Bloom</content>
	<content contentuid="hc1ab66dcg4203g4546gbfbcg2c625712df53" version="1">REQUIRES: Soul Sacred Focus
You bind a spirit of wild growth that enriches the land around you. Once per Long Rest you may cast Create Food and Water without expending a spell slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h06ddb55fg7834g4cf8g99ecg3ae4838578ec" version="1">Totem of the Eruption</content>
	<content contentuid="h30960f2egb2c3g4f39gb62bg6d125ebfe6bc" version="1"> You bind an elemental spirit that lends you its destructive power. Once per turn, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one of your Primal Magic spell slots to deal additional cold, fire, lightning, or thunder damage (your choice) to the target equal to 1d8 per Spell Slot level spent.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6c475c8dg6fd0g41c4g8b88g5ec386303bae" version="1">Totemic Eruption: Cold </content>
	<content contentuid="h21416c83gcbe6g4a29g8eaag025beb06db4a" version="1">Totemic Eruption: Fire </content>
	<content contentuid="h06186d62g64efg4171ga1c7g36b7567d210d" version="1">Totemic Eruption: Lightning</content>
	<content contentuid="h38267772g6462g4dd7gb9f0ga9998a7233dc" version="1">Totemic Eruption: Thunder</content>
	<content contentuid="h2c78433fg37cdg4ddfgb6d5g2f73407f311b" version="1">Unleash the wrath of your bound spirits dealing an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h5365d00ega1d6g423dgbea1g7bbd2d3d2ecf" version="1">Totem of Growth</content>
	<content contentuid="hd73ca0e1gb719g403bg8f86g956bcf928ea0" version="1">REQUIRES: Body Sacred Focus
 You bind a spirit of wild growth that can temporarily increase your size. Once per Short Rest you may cast the 'Enlarge' version of Enlarge/Reduce on yourself as a bonus action, without expending a spell slot or concentrating.</content>
	<content contentuid="he9ac54a3g62c7g4ddbg8189g05e47b1da175" version="1">Totem of the Grave</content>
	<content contentuid="h0387f6f8g98a4g4a5fg80cag9b5ade37270f" version="1">You bind a spirit of undead power which you can summon to your service. You learn Animate Dead and can cast it with your Primal Magic Spell Slots.</content>
	<content contentuid="hda000c1fgcfa7g4156g8cb0gc71833b403f7" version="1">Totem of Light</content>
	<content contentuid="h11ffa9f2g332bg46a0gbab0g72280a9d5e49" version="1">You bind a spirit of radiance that restores your spirit when you aid others. When you cast a spell of 1st-level or higher that restores hit points to a creature other than yourself, you gain temporary hit points equal to your Wisdom modifier. </content>
	<content contentuid="hd66f97b9g087cg4ccfga3afgeb949d6cd389" version="1">Totem of Mirth</content>
	<content contentuid="hd9020d67ga393g4bbag968cg7a90aa22ec04" version="1">REQUIRES: Heart Sacred Focus
You bind a spirit of revelry and life that grants you renewed vigor. Once per long rest, you can use a bonus action to grant yourself temporary hit points equal to your Shaman level.</content>
	<content contentuid="hef950eb7g5e22g41fag806fge6a0563c8897" version="1">Totem of the Mystic</content>
	<content contentuid="h2bd15106gf6e5g4ff2ga595geca59244f6ad" version="1">REQUIRES: Mind Sacred Focus
 You bind a spirit of secret knowledge that grants you the ability to peer into the minds of others. You are permanently under the effects of Detect Thoughts.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb4c95854g2a92g4c8dg83cbgd2789c95175b" version="1">Totem of the Wild</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f29409dg4982g4017gbc91gb981127e4f3b" version="1"> You bind a bestial spirit which you can call to your aid. Once per Long Rest, you can cast Summon Beast at a level equal to your Primal Magic slots without expending a slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h79e95ba0g649bg4e45gbfccg6b9b58b9025e" version="1">Totem of Wrath</content>
	<content contentuid="hd5cedd4bgce5fg4d10g869bgb8b5efb5cf23" version="1"> You bind a spirit of anger that increases your power. When a creature fails its saving throw against Totemic Assault, you can add your Wisdom modifier to the damage roll.</content>
	<content contentuid="h946200b3g29efg4716gaea9g9006964d2330" version="1">Totem of the Hunt</content>
	<content contentuid="hb7ec2c4egf368g4437g82b7gda49b0531cee" version="1">You bind a spirit of the Wild Hunt that enhances your ferocity. Once per turn, you can grant yourself advantage on an attack roll if your target is within 5 feet of one of your allies.</content>
	<content contentuid="he08126ccga24bg4303ga9f4g4939c9027010" version="1">Totem of the Dawn</content>
	<content contentuid="h811a362eg613fg4e40g95d5g2ed750cc8f46" version="1">You bind a spirit of radiance which you can shield creatures from death. Once per Long Rest, you can cast death ward on a creature of your choice, without expending a spell slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h96be6576g81a8g465bg97f7g573b1b39287f" version="1">Totem of Midnight</content>
	<content contentuid="hb5291b99g7d21g4ca7g98ccg060d4915cab9" version="1">You bind a sinister spirit which you can call to you. Once per long rest, you may cast Summon Shadowspawn at the level of your Primal Magic slots, without expending a spell slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h42a67bebg18dfg4106g9d6eg67dd48867ae4" version="1">Totem of the Sun</content>
	<content contentuid="hb380657fg5df7g4d5egabeeg513c356105d0" version="1"> You bind a spirit of radiance that allows you to succeed when all hope seems lost. Once per short rest, when you fail a saving throw, you can choose to re-roll, possibly turning a failure into a success.</content>
	<content contentuid="h22b7fddbg92adg4989g8f3cg98f32fc17b20" version="1">Totem of the Vine</content>
	<content contentuid="h74d89ea9g6a54g4edcgb870g55c81d31ed07" version="1">You bind a spirit of wild growth which lends you the power to restrain your foes. You can cast Ensnaring Strike at 1st-level, at will, without expending a spell slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="h35b9e325gc109g46bbg89c0ga20c550db613" version="1">Totem of Binding</content>
	<content contentuid="h0190ce5fg68a5g4da8gaa5dg2ff954d1e327" version="1"> You can quickly bind a spirit to regain some of your power. Once per long rest, you can use a Bonus Action to regain one of your expended Primal Magic spell slots.</content>
	<content contentuid="h89eec00dgfdd5g49f6gb577gf0f7e21bf738" version="1">Totem of the Eclipse</content>
	<content contentuid="hec650e1cg3ef9g4964gaad0g0d7c3cec0eec" version="1"> You bind a powerful spirit that grants you resistance to the arcane. You gain resistance to all damage from spells.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4a01d6b6g5c97g4fe6g8c8dgbe05f3879599" version="1">Totem of the Elements</content>
	<content contentuid="hf04fff9fgccb3g4c6cg8f08g09d5020816d2" version="1">You bind an elemental spirit which you can call to your aid. Once per Short Rest, you can cast Summon Elemental without expending a Spell Slot.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcffbba4eg347fg4c3egbe4dg551ac496ac05" version="1">Totem of the Sapling</content>
	<content contentuid="he26fdd94g4c1cg4fbcga20cgaf20b263cf9b" version="1"> You bind a powerful spirit of wild growth which blesses your body with wondrous regeneration. At the start of each of your turns, you regain hit points equal to your Wisdom modifier, so long as you have no more than half of your hit points left and are not downed.</content>
	<content contentuid="heb367924ge5a6g478cgaac5g63d6bb284006" version="1">Totem of the Skies</content>
	<content contentuid="h9d9b9e5cg35d1g4017g9a7eg01cd7b500104" version="1">You bind a powerful spirit of elemental air which propels you through the air. You can now fly at will using your movement speed.</content>
</contentList>